Just deux it.
Hot Shots! Part Deux is a action, comedy, war film directed by Jim Abrahams.
Topper Harley is found to be working as an odd-job-man in a monastery.
The CIA want him to lead a rescue mission into Iraq, to rescue the last rescue team, who went in to
rescue the last rescue team—who went in to rescue hostages left behind after Desert Storm.
Topper Harley, played by Charlie Sheen.
President Thomas 'Tug' Benson, played by Lloyd Bridges.
Ramada Rodham Hayman, played by Valeria Golino.
Col. Denton Walters, played by Richard Crenna.
Dexter Hayman, played by Rowan Atkinson.
Commander Arvid Harbinger, played by Miguel Ferrer.
Part Deux, also known as Hot Shots!
2, is a 1993 American parody film directed by Jim
Abrahams and written by Abrahams and Pat Proft.
It stars Charlie Sheen, Lloyd Bridges, Valeria Golino, Richard Crenna,
Brenda Bakke, Miguel Ferrer, Rowan Atkinson, and Jerry Haleva.
A sequel to Hot Shots!
(1991), it is a parody of Rambo: First Blood Part II (1985) and Rambo III (1988), and
follows a small of group soldiers on a mission to save prisoners of war in Iraq.
The film explores themes of rescue, swordplay,
liberation of hostage, secret agent, parody.
The tone is lighthearted.